in this lecture we will make the
在这堂课中，我们将使
Microsoft Loop logo I go to file import
Microsoft循环徽标我转到文件导入
I select the logo and click on open
我选择徽标并点击打开
I click on OK I will create a new layer
我点击确定，我将创建一个新的层
and lock the layer with the image I
并使用图像i锁定该层
click on the ellipse tool I hold down
点击我按住的椭圆工具
control and drag a circle I click on the
控件并拖动一个圆圈，然后单击
fill and stroke tab I drag the alpha of
我拖动的Alpha的填充和描边选项卡
the fill to zero I press the plus once
填到零我按一次加号
to set it to one percent I do this so I
为了将其设置为1%，我这样做是为了
see only the stroke but I can still drag
只看到笔划，但我仍然可以拖动
the shapes easily around by dragging
通过拖动可以轻松地将形状四处移动
their fill
他们的满足感
I hold shift plus control and size the
我按住Shift+Ctrl键并调整
circle
圆
I duplicate the circle by pressing Ctrl
我通过按Ctrl复制圆
d
D
I hold shift and click on the larger
我按住Shift键并单击较大的
Circle I go to path difference
圆圈我去路径差
I name the path Circle
我将这条路径命名为Circle
now I click on the rectangle tool and
现在我点击矩形工具，然后
drag a rectangle
拖动一个矩形
I activate snapping
我激活了捕捉
I press the space bar to go to the
我按空格键进入
select tool I drag the rectangle against
选择我在其上拖动矩形的工具
the Inner Circle until I see corner to
内圈，直到我看到角落到
smooth node
平滑节点
I drag the handle down until it snaps
我把手柄往下拖，直到它嘎吱作响
and I drag to the left until it snaps
我向左拖拽，直到它折断
I duplicate the rectangle I click on the
我复制了我在
rectangle again so I see the rotation
再次使用矩形，这样我就可以看到旋转
handles
手柄
I hold Ctrl and drag a corner until I
按住Ctrl键并拖动一个角，直到我
rotate it 90 degrees
将其旋转90度
I drag the rectangle to the corner until
我把矩形拖到角落里，直到
it snaps
它折断了
I click on the Node tool and select add
我单击节点工具，然后选择添加
corners
转角
I drag the circle at the bottom right
我拖动右下角的圆圈
until I see handle to Corner
直到我看到拐角的把手
I press the space bar I call the shape
我按下空格键，我称其为图形
gradient left and I call the rectangle
渐变向左，我称该矩形为
below gradient bottom now I duplicate
下面的渐变底部现在我复制
the Layer Two Times by pressing Ctrl D
按Ctrl D键按两次层
to recreate the gradient of the logo I
要重建徽标的渐变，请执行以下操作
will need to make three gradients I will
将需要做三个渐变我会
call the top layer gradient left and the
将顶层称为渐变左侧，并将
layer below I call gradient bottom the
下面的层我称之为渐变底部
bottom layer will have a general
底层会有一个通用的
gradient the left gradient goes from
渐变左侧的渐变来自
dark purple to a lighter purple
深紫色到浅紫色
to create the shape for this I don't
要为此创建形状，我不
need the bottom rectangle so I will
我需要底部的矩形，所以我会
delete it
删除它
I hide the other layers so I can better
我隐藏了其他的层，这样我就能更好地
see what I am doing I will also hide
看到我在做什么，我也会躲起来
gradient left for a moment I click on
向左渐变了一会儿，我点击了
the circle and select the node tool I
圆圈并选择节点工具i
only need the top left part of the
只需要
circle
圆
so I will cut the circle
所以我要把圆圈剪掉
I drag over the top nodes to select them
我将鼠标拖到顶部节点上以选择它们
then I click on break path at selected
然后，我单击选定位置处的中断路径
nodes I also do this for the nodes at
节点我也对位于的节点执行此操作
the left then I click on the most write
然后我点击左边写得最多的
node I hold Ctrl and scroll forward
节点I按住Ctrl键并向前滚动
until all nodes are selected I also
在选择所有节点之前，我还
control scroll on the right node of the
控件的右侧节点上的滚动控件。
Inner Circle I have now selected all
内圈我现在已经选择了全部
nodes that I don't need so I press
我不需要的节点，所以我按
delete now I want to close the gaps I
现在删除我想弥合我的差距
drag over the right nodes I click on
将鼠标拖到我单击的右侧节点上
join selected endnodes with a new
将选定端节点与新的
segment I also do this for the bottom
片段I也是为底部这样做的
nodes
节点
I make gradient left visible again and
我再次使渐变变得可见
shift click on it I go to path Union I
Shift单击它，我将转到路径Union I
call the shape gradient left
将形状渐变称为左侧
now let's create the shape for the
现在，让我们为
bottom gradient I hide gradient left and
底部渐变I隐藏渐变左侧和
make gradient bottom visible for the
使渐变底部对
bottom gradient I don't need gradient
底部渐变我不需要渐变
left so I delete it I hide gradient
向左，所以我删除它，我隐藏渐变
bottom for the bottom gradient I need
底部用于我需要的底部渐变
the bottom right of the circle so I
圆圈的右下角，所以我
repeat what I did before I select the
重复我在选择
nodes at the right and break the path at
节点位于右侧，并在
the selected nodes then I select the
选定的节点，然后选择
nodes at the bottom and break the path
节点位于底部，并中断路径
there
那里
I click on the most left node and
我点击最左边的节点，
control scroll forward until all nodes
Ctrl向前滚动，直到所有节点
are selected I also control scroll on
被选中时，我也控制滚动
the left note of the Inner Path then I
内道的左音符然后是我
press delete I select the top nodes and
按Delete键选择顶部节点，然后
join them and I select the left nodes
加入它们，我选择左边的节点
and connect them I make gradient bottom
然后把它们连接起来，我做了渐变底部
visible again and shift-click on it then
再次可见，然后按住Shift键并单击它
I go to path Union I call the shape
我去PATH UNION，我叫它形状
gradient Bottom now I will use the shape
渐变底部现在我将使用形状
Builder tool to create the logo shape
用于创建徽标形状的构建器工具
I hide gradient bottom and make the
我隐藏渐变底部并使
layer below visible I select all three
下面的层可见，我将三个都选中
shapes I click on the shape Builder tool
我在形状构建器工具上单击的形状
I see I have an unwanted connection so I
我发现我有一个不想要的连接，所以我
click on the X icon to exit I go to path
单击X图标退出I Go to Path
fracture I click on the shape Builder
断开我单击形状构建器
tool again I will now combine the shapes
工具，现在我将组合这些形状
I want
我想要
I remove superfluent nodes
我移除多余的结节
I call the shape General shape now let's
我把这个形状称为一般形状，现在让我们
place the gradients I will make the logo
放置我将制作徽标的渐变
layer visible to see the colors I will
层可见，我会看到颜色
drag the image to the left I click on
将图像拖到左侧，我点击
the fill and stroke tab for my fill I
我的填充的填充和描边选项卡为
need a linear gradient I click on the
需要一个线性渐变，我点击
gradient tool
渐变工具
then I click on the dropper tool because
然后我点击滴管工具，因为
the left gradient will be on top I need
左侧的渐变将在我需要的顶部
the general gradient to go from Blue to
从蓝色到蓝色的一般渐变
the lighter purple
浅紫色
so I click on the left color stop and
所以我点击左边的色标，然后
Sample the blue then I click on the
试一下蓝色，然后我点击
right color stop and Sample the light
正确的颜色停止并采样灯光
purple now I will position the color
现在我要把颜色定位为紫色
stops I drag the left color stop down
停靠点我向下拖动左侧颜色停靠点
and the right color stop up
和正确的颜色停止
I click on stroke and click on no paint
我点击笔划，然后点击无油漆
I go back to my layers now let's color
我回到我的层次，现在让我们涂上颜色
gradient left
左侧渐变
I go to fill and stroke again I click on
我去填充，然后再一次点击
fill and click on linear gradient I
填充并单击线性渐变I
click on the left color stop and Sample
点击左边的色标并取样
the dark purple then I select the right
然后我选了右边的深紫色
color stop and Sample the light purple
停止上色并品尝浅紫色
then I position the color stops
然后我定位色标
I click on stroke and click on no paint
我点击笔划，然后点击无油漆
I go back to my layers the third
我回到了我的第三层
gradient is to improve the gradient on
渐变是为了提高渐变上的
the bottom I go to fill and stroke and
我去填充底部，然后划一划
set fill to gradient
将填充设置为渐变
I click on the left color stop and
我点击左边的色标，然后
Sample the blue and for the right color
试一试蓝色，然后选择合适的颜色
stop I also sample the blue but I set
停止，我也试了蓝色，但我设定了
its Alpha to zero
它的Alpha归零
I position the color stops
我对色标进行定位
and finally I will place the shadow I go
最后，我会把我要去的影子
to my layers I duplicate gradient left
我将左侧渐变复制到我的层
that will become the shadow in fill and
那将成为填充物和
stroke I select flat color
笔划我选择纯色
I drag Alpha to 100 and I set blur to
我将Alpha拖动到100，然后将模糊设置为
about 30 percent
约30%
in my layers I call the shape shadow
在我的层次中，我将形状称为阴影
I will use General shape to mask the
我将使用常规形状来遮罩
shadow
阴影
I right click on it and choose set clip
我右击它并选择Set Clip(设置剪辑
group I drag the clip group in the
组I将剪辑组拖动到
gradient left layer I place the clip
渐变左层我放置剪辑
group on the bottom I open the clip
底部的群组我打开剪辑
group I will now drag the shadow in the
小组我现在将拖着阴影
clip group
夹组
to remove the shadow at the top I click
要删除顶部的阴影，我点击
on the Node tool I click on the top node
在“节点”工具上，我单击顶部节点
and press delete
并按delete
I will also delete the node below and to
我还将删除下面的节点并到
make gradient bottom visible again I
让渐变底部再次可见，
drag it below the shadow
把它拖到阴影下
I will delete the other layers all
我会删除所有其他层
shapes of the vectorized logo are now in
现在已推出了Vector的形状
a single layer
单层